Finding Aid to The Georgia O'Keeffe Foundation Photographs MS.57
Georgia O'Keeffe Museum
- BoBo, before 1968; 2006.6.321; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 4 7/8 x 7 inches; Doris Bry stamp on verso .Handwritten on verso: 22494-21Handwritten on verso: "Bobo per D.B."," Bry 41","22494-21" Stamp on verso: "MAY NOT BE USED WITHOUT PERMISSION OF"," DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86 ST. NEW YORK 28, 9.Y."
- BoBo, before 1968; 2006.6.322; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 4 15/16 x 7 inches; Doris Bry stamp on verso .Handwritten on verso: 22494-20Handwritten on verso: "Bobo per D.B."," Bry 42","22494-20" Stamp on verso: "MAY NOT BE USED WITHOUT PERMISSION OF"," DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86 ST. NEW YORK 28, 9.Y."
- Chia, before 1968; 2006.6.323; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 6 7/8 x 5 inches; Doris Bry stamp on verso .Handwritten on verso: 22494-16Handwritten on verso: "Chia per D.B."," Bry 43","22494-16" Stamp on verso: "MAY NOT BE USED WITHOUT PERMISSION OF"," DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86 ST. NEW YORK 28, 9.Y."
- Chow Dog, 1974; 2006.6.324; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 9 7/8 x 8 inches; Doris Bry stamp on verso .Handwritten on verso: 8569 18927-cr 16A 2Handwritten on verso:"8569 18927-CR IGA" (?) ,"2" (circled) Stamp on verso: "Please credit photo to: DORIS BRY 11 EAST 73 ST. NEW YORK, N.Y. 1002128"
  This is not one of Georgia O'Keeffe's dogs.
- Chow Dogs, 1974; 2006.6.325; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 15/16 x 4 7/8 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Blue Female 10/3/1974 Sire - Ch. Meeko'; Handwritten on verso: 058 20869-c1Handwritten on verso:"By Doris Bry", "blue female 10/3/74","058 20869-C1" (?), "$3", "2" (circled), "Sire - Ch. Meeko"
  Not Georgia O'Keeffe's dogs.
- Chow Dogs, 1974; 2006.6.326; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 7/8 x 4 15/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: '10/3/1974 Inca's Brother'; Handwritten on verso: 05820869-9 #11 n 2Handwritten on verso: "By Doris Bry", "10/3/1974- Inca's brother","05820869-CR $11"(?), "2" (circled)
- Chow Dogs, 1974; 2006.6.327; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 7/8 x 4 15/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Ch. Titus 10/3/1974 Inca's Father'; Handwritten on verso: 58 20889-9 #15 2Handwritten on verso:"By Doris Bry", "Ch. Titus 10/3/1974", "Inca's father", "058 20869-9 $11" ,"2" (circled)
- Chow Dogs, 1974; 2006.6.328; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 7/8 x 4 15/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: '10/3/1974 Titus Inca's father'Handwritten on verso: "By Doris Bry","10/3/74 Titus-Inca's father", "058 20860-CR $15" (?), "2" (circled)
- Chow Dogs, 1974; 2006.6.329; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 7/8 x 4 15/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Jubilee Jr. litter 10/3/1974 blue male red female. Female not for sale.'Handwritten on verso: "By Doris Bry","10/3/74", "Jubilee Jr. litter", "blue male red female", "female-not for sale", "058 20869-CL 17" (?), "2" (circled)
- Chow Dogs, 1974; 2006.6.330; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 15/16 x 4 15/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Ch. Titus Inca's father 10/3/1974'Handwritten on verso: "By Doris Bry", "Ch. Titus Inca's father 10/3/74", "058 20869-9 $12" (?), "2" (circled)
- Chow Dogs, 1974; 2006.6.331; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 7/8 x 4 15/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: '10/3/1974 Inca's brother'Handwritten on verso: "10/3/74 Inca's brother", "058 20869-02 $17" (?), "2" (circled)
- Chow Dogs, 1974; 2006.6.332; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 15/16 x 4 15/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Blue male 10/3/1974 Jubilee Jr. Litter'Handwritten on verso: "blue male", "10/3/74", "Jubilee Jr. Litter", "058 20869-CR $1" (?), "2" (circled)
- Chow Dogs, 1974; 2006.6.333; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 15/16 x 5 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'sire of blue female puppy'Handwritten on verso: 'sire of blue female puppy'; '10/3/74 - Ch. Meeko- "hairless wonder."'; '058 20869-C2 $14 2' 2 is circled
- Chow Dogs, 1974; 2006.6.334; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 4 15/16 x 4 1/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Titus 10/3/1974 Inca's father'; Handwritten on verso: 05820869-C1 #13Handwritten on verso: 'Titus 10/3/74 Inca's father'; '058 20869-C1 $13' 2 circled
- Chow Dogs, 1974; 2006.6.335; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 4 15/16 x 4 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Sandy 10/3/1974'; Handwritten on verso: 058 20869-4 #9Handwritten on verso: 'Sandy 10/3/1974'; '058 20869-4 #9'
- Chow Dogs, 1974; 2006.6.336; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 4 15/16 x 4 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Sandy 10/3/1974 Cassandra'Handwritten on verso: 'Sandy 10/3/74 Cassandra'; '058 020869-C1 $8 2' 2 is circled
- Chow Dogs, 1974; 2006.6.337; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 4 x 5 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Blue male 10/3/1974 Jubilee Jr. litter'Handwritten on verso: 'blue male 10/3/74'; 'Jubilee Jr. litter'; '058 20869-C2 $3 2'. 2 is circled
- Chow Dogs, 1974; 2006.6.338; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 15/16 x 9 7/8 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'blue male Jubilee Jr. Litter 10/3/74'Handwritten on verso: 'blue male Jubilee Jr. Litter 10/3/74'; '1060 20869 - $5 3' 3 is circled
- Chow Dogs, 1974; 2006.6.339; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 9 7/8 x 8 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Cassandra 'Sandy' 10/3/74'Handwritten on verso: 'Cassandra 'Sandy' 10/3/74'; '1060 20869-C1 $10 2' 2 is circled
- Chow Dogs, 1974; 2006.6.340; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 9 7/8 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'blue male Jubilee Jr. Litter 10/3/74'Handwritten on verso: 'blue male Jubilee Jr. Litter 10/3/74'; '10620896-C2 $2 3' 3 is circled
- Chow Dogs, 1974; 2006.6.341; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 9 15/16 x 8 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Mrs. Earle and red female puppy (n.f.s.) 10/3/74'Handwritten on verso: 'Mrs. Earle & red female puppy (n.f.s.) 10/3/74'; '106 20869-C2 $6 3' 3 is circled
- Chow Dogs, 1974; 2006.6.342; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 9 7/8 x 8 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Cassandra 'Sandy' 10/3/74'Handwritten on verso: 'Cassandra 'Sandy' 10/3/74'; '106 20869-C1 $7 2' 2 is circled
- Chow Dogs, 1974; 2006.6.343; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 9 7/8 x 8 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'blue female puppy s. Ch. Meeko 10/3/74'Handwritten on verso: 'blue female puppy s. Ch. Meeko 10/3/74'; '1060 20869-C1 $1 3' 3 is circled
- Chow Dogs, 1974; 2006.6.344; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 9 15/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Jubilee Jr. Litter the male on left red female not for sale on right. Best of there[sic] puppies shows desirable short nose 10/3/74'Handwritten on verso: 'Jubilee Jr. Litter the male on left, red female, not for sale ,on right. - Best of there[sic] puppies-shows desirable short nose 10/3/74'; '1060 20869-C1 $19 3" 3 is circled
- Chow Dogs, 1974; 2006.6.345; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 9 7/8 x 8 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Cassandra 'Sandy' 10/3/74'Handwritten on verso: 'Cassandra 'Sandy' 10/3/74'; '1060 20869- C1 $6 2' 2 is circled
- Chow Dogs, 1974; 2006.6.346; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 9 15/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'blue female puppy s. Ch. Meeko 10/3/74'Handwritten on verso: 'blue female puppy S. Ch. Meeko 10/3/74'; '1060 20869-C1 $5 3' 3 is circled
- Chow Dogs, 1974; 2006.6.347; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 9 7/8 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'blue female puppy s. Ch. Meeko 10/3/74'Handwritten on verso: 'blue female puppy S. Ch. Meeko 10/3/74'; '1060 20869-C1 $5 3' 3 is circled
- Chow Dogs, 1974; 2006.6.348; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches; Doris Bry stamp on versoHandwritten on verso: '523 1388 C2-22 3'; Stamp on verso: 'Please credit photograph to: DORIS BRY 11 EAST 73rd St. NEW YORK, N.Y. 10021'
- Chow Dogs, 1974; 2006.6.349; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 9 15/16 x 8 1/16 inches; Doris Bry stamp on versoHandwritten on verso: '523 1388 C2-210 3'; Stamp on verso: 'Please credit photograph to: DORIS BRY 11 EAST 73rd St. NEW YORK, N.Y. 10021'
- Jingo, 1972; 2006.6.350; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 10 inches; On verso: 'O'Keeffe Jingo'On verso: watermark: 'AGFO'
- Jingo, 1972; 2006.6.351; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 3 1/2 x 5 inches; On verso: 'From Doris Bry' '11/72'Handwritten on verso: 'from Doris Bry' '11/72', Kodak stamp Dec 72
- BoBo, 1962; 2006.6.352; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 9/16 x 4 15/16 inches; On verso: 'From Doris Bry'Handwritten on verso: 'Sept. 1962 from Doris Bry'
- Chia, 1962; 2006.6.353; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 9/16 x 4 15/16 inches; On verso: 'From Doris Bry' 'Sept 1962'Handwritten on verso: 'Sept. 1962- from Doris Bry'
- Lake Powell, 1970s; 2006.6.354; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 9 15/16 x 8 inches; Doris Bry stamp on versoHandwritten on verso: "BRY 23" "4-17"; Stamp on verso: "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N.Y."
- Lake Powell, 1970s; 2006.6.355; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 9 15/16 inches; Doris Bry stamp on verso and '9-7'Handwritten on verso: "BRY 24" '9-7'; Stamp on verso: 'DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86TH ST. NEW YORK 28, N.Y.'
- Lake Powell, 1970s; 2006.6.356; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 9 15/16 x 8 inches; Doris Bry stamp on verso and '9-4'Handwritten on verso: 'BRY 25' '9-4'; Stamp on verso: "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th, ST. NEW YORK, 28 N.Y."
- Lake Powell, 1970s; 2006.6.357; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 9 15/16 x 8 inches; Doris Bry stamp on versoHandwritten on verso: 'BRY 26' '9-2'; Stamp on verso: 'DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86th ST. NEW YORK 28, N.Y.'
- Chama River, circa 1947-circa 1977; 2006.6.358; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 9 15/16 inches; Doris Bry stamp on verso and '22980-25'Handwritten on verso: '22980-25'"BRY 28"; Stamp on verso: 'PHOTOGRAPHED BY: DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86TH NEW YORK, 28, N.Y."
- Chama River, circa 1947-circa 1977; 2006.6.359; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 9 15/16 x 8 inches; Doris Bry stamp on verso and '22980-24'Handwritten on verso: "BRY 27" '22980-24'; Stamp on verso: "PHOTOGRAPHED BY" "DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86TH NEW YORK, 28, N.Y."
- Chama River, circa 1947-circa 1977; 2006.6.360; Bry, Doris, 1920-2014; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 1/16 x 9 15/16 inches; Doris Bry stamp on verso and '22980-23'Handwritten on verso: "BRY 29" '22980-23' Stamp on verso: "PHOTOGRAPHED BY' 'DORIS BRY 510 EAST 86TH NEW YORK 28, N.Y."
- Maria Chabot Cutting Aspen on the Martinez Ranch, 1947; 2006.6.361; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 7/8 x 4 1/4 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Spring-when we got the new tractor'Handwritten on verso: 'Spring-When we got the new tractor'
- Maria Chabot Cutting Aspen on the Martinez Ranch, 1947; 2006.6.362; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 2 15/16 x 4 9/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'This is what made the ceiling in that building that's too big.'Handwritten on verso: 'This is what made the ceiling in that building that' too big.'
- Cutting Aspen on the Martinez Ranch, 1947; 2006.6.363; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 3/8 x 4 1/2 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'This is high up-The Martinez Ranch'Handwritten on verso: 'This is high up-the Martinez Ranch'
- Maria Chabot Cutting Aspen on the Martinez Ranch, 1947; 2006.6.364; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 3 1/4 x 4 3/4 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Cutting aspen in March '47'Handwritten on verso: "cutting aspen in March '47"
- Alfred Stieglitz, 1929-1946; 2006.6.366; Marcus, Elli, 1899-1977; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 9 7/8 x 8 1/16 inches
  Profile head shot of Alfred Stieglitz wearing glasses and looking down, tousled hair, wearing a white shirt and vest, blurred background.
- Bust of Georgia O'Keeffe by Una Hanbury, 1968; 2006.6.369; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 10 x 8 1/16 inches; Charles Uht stamp on versoStamp on verso: "please credit: PHOTOGRAPH BY CHARLES UHT 511 EAST 84 ST., N. Y. 28, N. Y. TELEPHONE REGENT 4-8866"; Handwritten on verso: "2"
- Bust of Georgia O'Keeffe by Una Hanbury, 1968; 2006.6.370; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 9 7/8 x 8 inches; FRAMED
- Bust of Georgia O'Keeffe by Una Hanbury, 1968; 2006.6.371; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 9 7/8 x 7 15/16 inches; FRAMED
- Bust of Georgia O'Keeffe by Una Hanbury, 1968; 2006.6.372; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 9 15/16x 7 15/16 inches
- Bust of Georgia O'Keeffe by Una Hanbury, 1968; 2006.6.373; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 9 15/16 x 7 15/16 inches
- Bust of Georgia O'Keeffe by Una Hanbury, 1968; 2006.6.374; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 9 15/16 x 7 15/16 inches
- Bust of Georgia O'Keeffe by Una Hanbury, 1968; 2006.6.375; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 10 x 8 1/16 inches; Stamp on verso from National Portrait GalleryStamp on verso: "NOT TO BE REPRODUCED WITHOUT WRITTEN PERMISSION OF THE NATIONAL PORTRAIT GALLERY, SMITHSONIAN INSTITUTE, WASHINGTION, D.C."
- Bust of Georgia O'Keeffe by Una Hanbury, 1968; 2006.6.376; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 10 x 8 1/16 inches; Stamp on verso from National Portrait GalleryStamp on verso: "NOT TO BE REPRODUCED WITHOUT WRITTEN PERMISSION OF THE NATIONAL PORTRAIT GALLERY, SMITHSONIAN INSTITUTE, WASHINGTION, D.C."
- Portrait of O'Keeffe by Una Hanbury, 1968; 2006.6.377; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 9 15/16 x 8 1/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: "Photo for Georgia O'Keeffe", "Una Hanbury"Handwritten on verso: "Photo for Georgia O'Keeffe", "Una Hanbury"
- Portrait of O'Keeffe by Una Hanbury, 1968; 2006.6.378; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 10 x 8 1/8 inches; Handwritten on verso: "Photo for Georgia O'Keeffe", "Una Hanbury"; Post-it attached to verso: "Una Hanbury Sculpture (photo sent 12.10.68)"Handwritten on verso: "Photo for Georgia O'Keeffe", "Una Hanbury"; Post-it attached to verso: "Una Hanbury Sculpture (photo sent 12.10.68)"
- American Academy Exhibition, 1963; 2006.6.379; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 1/8 x 10 inches
  Copyright Budd Waintrob
- Abiquiu House, Bedroom, 1995; 2006.6.381; Hardaway, Lisa; Hester, Paul; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 10 7/8 x 14 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Lisa Carol Hardaway and Paul Hester 1995'Handwritten on verso: "PAUL HESTER + Lisa Carol Handaway", "HESTER and HANDAWAY 2"
  Copyright Hester + Hardaway Photogypsies Architectural Photography
- Abiquiu House, Sitting Room, 1995; 2006.6.382; Hardaway, Lisa; Hester, Paul; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 10 7/8 x 13 15/16 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Lisa Carol Hardaway and Paul Hester 1995'Handwritten on verso: "Lisa Carol Handaway + PAUL HESTER" ,"HESTER and HANDAWAY 1"
- Abiquiu House (contact sheet), 1965; 2006.6.383; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 10 x 8 1/16 inches; Stamp on verso: "THIS PRINT IS SOLD FOR REFERENCE ONLY POSITIVELY NOT TO BE RESOLD, REPRODUCED, OR SYNDICATED WITHOUT SPECIAL PERMISSION OF THE PHOTOGRAPHER REF. # BALTAZAR KORAB 950 N. HUNTER BLVD., BIRMINGHAM, MICHIGAN MI. 6-9889" Handwritten on verso: "KORAB 13"
- Abiquiu House (contact sheets), circa 1993; 2006.6.401; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 10 x 8 inches; Printed on verso: 'THIS PAPER MANUFACTURED BY KODAK' Handwritten on verso: 'BARSOTTI 2'
- Abiquiu House (contact sheets), circa 1993; 2006.6.402; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 10 x 8 inches; Printed on verso: 'THIS PAPER MANUFACTURED BY KODAK' Handwritten on verso: 'BARSOTTI 1'
- Abiquiu House, circa 1917; 2006.6.403; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 10 x 8 1/8 inches; Handwritten on verso: '[double exposure] Jose Martinez Chavez residence (G. O'Keeffe residence) Abiquiu New Mexico 1917'. Stamp of Kenneth ChapmanHandwritten on verso: '[double-exposure] Jose Martinez Chavez residence (G. O'Keeffe residence) Abiquiu New Mexico ca 1917 ', 'Kenneth Chapman 28691'; Stamp on verso: 'NOTICE This photograph is for study purposes only. It must not be reproduced in any form or publicly exhibited in any way without written permission from the owner and must be accompanied by this required credit lines: Photo by Courtesy Museum New Mexico Neg. NO.'; Handwritten on verso: '28691' 'Chaomas 3' ?
- Abiquiu House, circa 1917; 2006.6.404; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 9 15/16 x 8 1/8 inches; Handwritten on verso: '[double exposure] Jose Martinez Chavez residence (G. O'Keeffe residence) Abiquiu New Mexico 1917'. Stamp of Kenneth ChapmanHandwritten on verso: '[double exposure] Jose Martinez Chavez residence (G. O'Keeffe residence) Abiquiu New Mexico 1917'. Stamp on verso: 'NOTICE This photograph is for study purposes only. It must not be reproduced in any form or publicly exhibited in any way without written permission from the owner and must be accompanied by this required credit lines: Photo by Courtesy Museum New Mexico Neg. NO.' Handwritten on verso: '28690' 'CHAOMAS? ' 'Kenneth Chapman'
- Abiquiu House, circa 1917; 2006.6.405; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 10 x 8 1/8 inches; Handwritten on verso: '[double exposure] Jose Martinez Chavez residence (G. O'Keeffe residence) Abiquiu New Mexico 1917'. Stamp of Kenneth ChapmanHandwritten on verso: '[double exposure] Jose Martinez Chavez residence (G. O'Keeffe residence) Abiquiu New Mexico'. Stamp on verso: 'NOTICE This photograph is for study purposes only. It must not be reproduced in any form or publicly exhibited in any way without written permission from the owner and must be accompanied by this required credit lines: Photo by Courtesy Museum New Mexico Neg. NO.' Handwritten on verso: '28656' 'Chaomas 1' ? 'Kenneth Chapman'
- Church of St. Thomas, circa 1950; 2006.6.406; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 5 1/8 x 7 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Church of St. Thomas Abiquiu, New Mexcio ca. 1950'; Stamp of Tyler Dingee; Museum of New Mexico: negative number 7405Handwritten on verso: 'Church of St. Thomas Abiquiu, New Mexcio ca. 1950'; Stamp of Tyler Dingee; Museum of New Mexico: negative number 7405' 'Tyler Dingee' '7485'
- Church of St. Thomas, circa 1945; 2006.6.407; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 5 1/16 x 7 inches; Handwritten on verso: 'Church of St. Thomas Abiquiu, New Mexcio ca. 1950'; Stamp of George Fitzpatrick; Museum of New Mexico: negative number 55453Handwritten on verso: 'Church of St. Thomas Abiquiu, New Mexcio ca. 1950'; 'George Fitzpatrick 55453' 'FITZPATRICK 1'; Museum of New Mexico: negative number 55453
- Abiquiu House, Detail, 1960; 2006.6.408; Gilpin, Laura, 1891-1979; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 9 15/16 inches; Amon Carter Museum label on verso: Title - Architecture: O'Keeffe Residence.label on verso: Amon Carter Museum, Title - Architecture: O'Keeffe Residence, Artist- Laura Gilpin, 1960; stamp on verso: study purposes only
  Copyright Amon Carter Museum of American Art
- Abiquiu House, Sitting Room from Dining Room, 1960; 2006.6.409; Gilpin, Laura, 1891-1979; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 9 15/16 inches; Amon Carter Museum label on verso: Title - Architecture: O'Keeffe Residence.label on verso: Amon Carter Museum, Title - Architecture: O'Keeffe Residence, Artist- Laura Gilpin, 1960; stamp on verso: study purposes only
- Abiquiu House, Sitting Room from Dining Room, 1960; 2006.6.410; Gilpin, Laura, 1891-1979; 1 Photographic Prints copy print 7 15/16 x 10 1/8 inches; Amon Carter Museum label on verso: Title - Architecture: O'Keeffe Residence.Printed on recto: 'KODAK- S AFETY-FILM 16 16' vertical and reversed; Stamp on recto: 'PRINTED BY AMON CARTER MUSEUM'; Stamp on verso: 'NOTICE This photograph is for study purposes. It must not be reproduced in any form or publicly exhibited in any way without written permission from the owner must be accompanied by these required credit lines: Photo by Courtesy Museum New Mexico', 'Courtesy Laura Gilpin Collection
- Abiquiu House, Indian Room, 1960; 2006.6.411; Gilpin, Laura, 1891-1979; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 7 15/16 x 9 15/16 inches; Amon Carter Museum label on verso: Title - Architecture: O'Keeffe Residence.label on verso: Amon Carter Museum, Title - Architecture: O'Keeffe Residence, Artist- Laura Gilpin, 1960; stamp on verso: study purposes only
- Abiquiu House, Indian Room, 1960; 2006.6.412; Gilpin, Laura, 1891-1979; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 8 x 9 15/16 inches; Amon Carter Museum label on verso: Title - Architecture: O'Keeffe Residence.Stamp on recto: "PRINTED BY THE AMON CARTER MUSEUM" NOTICE: This photograph is for study purposes. It must not be reproduced in any form or publicly exhibited in any way without written permission from the owner and must be accompanied by the credit line: Courtesy Laura Gilpin Collection
- Abiquiu House, Indian Room, 1960; 2006.6.413; Gilpin, Laura, 1891-1979; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 7 15/16 x 10 1/16 inches; Amon Carter Museum label on verso: Title - Architecture: O'Keeffe Residence.Stamp on recto: 'PRINTED BY AMON CARTER MUSEUM'; Printed on recto: "KODAK S AFETY- FILM 15"; Printed on verso: "Agfa"; Stamp on verso: "NOTICE: This photograph is for study purposes only. It must not be reproduced in any form or publicly exhibited in any way without written permission of the owner and must be accompanied by the credit line: Courtesy Laura Gilpin Collection
- Abiquiu House, Dining Room, 1960; 2006.6.414; Gilpin, Laura, 1891-1979; 1 Photographic Prints color photograph 9 15/16 x 7 15/16 inches; Amon Carter Museum label on verso: Title - Architecture: O'Keeffe Residence.Label on verso: Amon Carter Museum, Title - Architecture: O'Keeffe Residence, Artist- Laura Gilpin, 1960; Stamp on verso: study purposes only
- Abiquiu House, Dining Room, 1960; 2006.6.415; Gilpin, Laura, 1891-1979; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 10 x 7 15/16 inches; Amon Carter Museum label on verso: Title - Architecture: O'Keeffe Residence.Stamp on recto: 'PRINTED BY AMON CARTER MUSEUM'; Printed on recto: 'KODAK S AFETY FILM 15 10' vertical and in reverse; Stamp on verso: "NOTICE This photograph is for study purposes only. It must not be reproduced in any form or publicly exhibited in any way without written permission of the owner and must be accompanied by the credit line: Courtesy Laura Gilpin Collection
- Abiquiu House, Dining Room, 1960; 2006.6.416; Gilpin, Laura, 1891-1979; 1 Photographic Prints gelatin silver print 10 x 7 15/16 inches; Amon Carter Museum label on verso: Title - Architecture: O'Keeffe Residence.Stamp on recto: 'PRINTED BY AMON CARTER MUSEUM'; Printed on recto: 'KODAK S AFETY FILM 15' vertical and in reverse; Stamp on verso: "NOTICE This photograph is for study purposes only. It must not be reproduced in any form or publicly exhibited in any way without written permission of the owner and must be accompanied by the credit line: Courtesy Laura Gilpin Collection